Guide to the Agnese Nelms Haury Papers TAM.163
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 1925-2003.
  - Douglas, William O.: Go East, Young Man (excerpts), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Duberman, Martin: "A Fellow Traveling," Review of Ronald Radosh's Commies in The Nation, Jul 16, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee: Alger Hiss Tribute, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Faulk, John Henry: "John Henry's Moving On," Austin American Statesman, Apr 14, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation: Henry Julian Wadleigh, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - FOIA Request, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Goldstein, Alvin H.: "The Unquiet Death of Julius and Ethel Rosenberg," Television Program, Feb 25, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Goutchkoff, Jean, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Government Records: Access, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Greene, Graham: The Human Factor, Book Review (excerpt), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Handwritten Notes: Re: Alger and Donald Hiss, John Lowenthal, etc., 1975-1977, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Harvard University Law Library: Hiss-Chambers case, Mar 26, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Hersh, Seymour M.: "Nixon's Last Cover-Up: The Tapes He Wants the Archives to Suppress," The New Yorker, Dec 14, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hiss Case: Court Documents (Brief, Memoranda, etc.), 1950, 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Hiss, Tony: Coordinator of Alger Hiss Projects, The Writers Room, 1991, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hiss, Tony: Coordinator of Alger Hiss Projects, The Writers Room, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hiss, Tony: Laughing Last, Book Reviews, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Hiss, Tony: The View from Alger's Window, Book Reviews, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hiss, Tony: Writings, 1970-1977, 1983, 1987-2001 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Hiss Case: FBI Forgeries, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Hiss Files: Harvard Collection (from William Reuben), 1949-1974 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Kalugin, Oleg: Clipping, Aug 13, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Correspondence, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Inquiries and Research re: Alger Hiss, 1999-2004 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Lee, Duncan, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Lesar, James: Lesar-Lowenthal Litigation with FBI, 1999, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Lowenthal, John: Correspondence, 1996, 2000, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - McClosky, Jeannie: Correspondence, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - McClosky, Jeannie: Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - The Nation, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Nation Institute: Alger Hiss Soviet Archives Project, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nation Institute: Publications and Research re: Hiss, Correspondence, 1992, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nation Institute: Publications and Research re: Hiss, Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Nation Institute: Publications and Research re: Hiss, Expenditure Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Foundation, 1977-1980, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Security Archive, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Security Archive, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Security Archive: Correspondence re: Maria Schmidt, Noel Field and Jay Peters, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Security Archive: Investigation Results from Archives in Hungary re: Noel Field, 1925-1931, 1946-1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Navasky, Victor, 1984, 1987, 1991-2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Nelson, Anna Katsen: Review of The Haunted Wood and Venona, Jun 25, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New York Times: Op-Eds, 1991-1993, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - New York University: Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nixon, Richard: Clippings, 1973-1976, 1987-1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nixon, Richard: "The Strange Case of Alger Hiss," Reader's Digest, Nov 1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Northern Arizona University: Center for Sustainable Environment, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pavlov, Vasili: Operation Snow, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Park, Rosemary: Correspondence, Dec 4, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Policy Review, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Popkin, Richard H and Barry Glassner: "Is Robert F. Bennett 'Deep Throat'," United Press International, Typescript, May 1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Correspondence, 1996, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Reuben, William: Book, Re: Hiss, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Reuben, William: Correspondence, 1980, 1990, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Reuben, William: Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Reuben, William: Oral History, Re: Hiss, 1984, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Richards, Christopher: Alger Hiss Archive, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Richards, Christopher: Alger Hiss Archive, Annual and Monthly Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Richards, Christopher: Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Richter, David: Correspondence, Jan 8, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Riesman, David: Individualism Reconsidered and Other Essays (excerpts), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Society of American Archivists: Statement re: Alger Hiss, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Some Questions and Answers Concerning Mr. Hiss and His Fordham Visit, Nov 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Symposia: Georgetown, Harvard and New York University, 1978, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Tanenhaus, Sam: Re: Whittaker Chambers, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Tiger, Edith: In Re: Alger Hiss, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - United Nations: Correspondence, May 7, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - University of Texas at Austin: Jamail Center for Legal Research, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Venona Article: Mailing, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Venona Cables: Re: "Ales", 1996, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Venona Cables: Re: Hiss, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Venona Conference, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Wadleigh, Henry Julian: FBI File, 1948-1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Watergate: Clippings and Nixon Interview on "Behind the Lines", 1973-1974, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Weinstein, Allen: Clippings and Correspondence, May 29, 1905, 1984, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Weiss, Louis: Correspondence, Oct 9, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - White, G. Edward: Writings re: Alger Hiss, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - White, Theodore: "Breach of Faith: The Fall of Richard Nixon" (condensed in Reader's Digest), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Yalta: Clipping re: Hiss, Jul 2, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Zeligs, Meyer, undated, 1960, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 49)